so let's discuss the memory or drink
waste solution for this in this
situation there is a store and then a
load to the same address so the load
obviously doesn't go to cache or memory
to get its value it's gonna get it from
the store but where does the store keep
its value the store doesn't broadcast
the result the result is broadcasts for
instructions that produce register
results so the store really never
broadcast this result so this is
definitely not true a reservation
station reservation stations never
provide any results to subsequent
instructions they only keep values
captured for the current instruction the
store doesn't even have a reservation
station so this is definitely not
correct
a Rob entry would keep a result for a
registered producing instruction between
the time it's been broadcast and the
time it commits but because the store is
not a register value producing
instruction it doesn't put its result in
a Rob entry in fact technically the
store doesn't have a result so this is
not correct the store does keep the
value it's going to store in the
load/store queue and if you remember
that is where the load searches for a
value when it's running to match its
address two addresses of previous stores
so this is the only correct answer